Guide to the Kate Millett papers, 1912-2002, bulk 1951-2001 RL.10070
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings and Speeches, 1928-2001, bulk 1968-1998; 42 boxes
  - Writings by Others, 1959-2001 and undated; 1969-2001; 3 boxes
    - Morgan, Robin, Reports from New York's Ground Zero, 2001 Sept. (Box W11)
    - Mosher, Loren, et al (eds.), Soteria typescript, 1995 (Box W11)
    - Murray, Michele, The Great Mother and Other Poems advance copy, 1974 (Box W11)
    - Pam, Eleanor, My Story typescript, circa 1993 (Box W11)
    - Pam, Eleanor, New Ground, undated (Box W11)
    - Proxpeale, Dane, Norman Mailer and the Mystery Woman, or, the Rape of the C--k, free-verse poem published in Esquire, Nov. 1972, typescript, circa 1972 (Box W11)
    - Ricciuti, Annie, poetry, undated (Box W11)
    - Simpkins, Kate, poetry, 1998 (Box W11)
    - Symons, Donald, The Evolution of Human Sexuality, precis of book, 1979 (Box W11)
    - Taylor, Kathleen, paper, 1997 (Box W11)
    - Thorington, Helen, typescript poetry and story, 1959 (Box W11)
    - Unidentified poetry, circa 1970 (Box W11)
    - Electronic format only: Unidentified poetry, 1991
      - file name Jim, 1991 Mar. 23 (Disk019) (Box W11)
    - Unidentified typescripts, undated (Box W11)
    - A Winter Tan, film synopsis, 1987 (Box W11)
    - Wheelan, Susan, Psychological Ecology: Group Origins of Individual Behavior typescript, undated (Box W11)
    - "Women Writers" [short manuscripts], 1973-1974 and undated (Box W11)
- Subject Files, 1957-2002; 18 boxes
  The Subject Files primarily include records from Millett's political involvements as a feminist, a mental health reformer, and a social activist; information that Millett collected for her writings and other projects; and personal papers related to travel, funding for the farm, and other issues. The early women's rights movement, from the late 1960s to the mid-1970s, is strongly represented. Various self-advocacy organizations within the psychiatric survivors movement, primarily from the mid 1980s to the mid 1990s, are also well-represented.
  The series includes the following subseries: Prisons, Psychiatric Survivors Movement, Torture, Travel, Women's Archives Project, and Women's Rights Movement. Within each subseries, files are organized in alphabetical order. A sequence of general subject files are placed at the end of the other subseries, in alphabetical order. Millett's own folder titles have been retained where possible.
  Included in this series are some documents in electronic format. These are listed alongside correponding physical folders in the collection from which diskettes were separated, or containing closely related documents. If there is no corresponding folder, the electronic files are marked "electronic format only." For each electronic document, the container list provides the file name, the date the file was last modified, and the number assigned to the original computer disk on which the file was received.
  Electronic records have been migrated to a library server. They may only be accessed in the Rubenstein Library's onsite reading room. Please contact the Rubenstein Library before coming to use these materials.
  - Prisons, 1969-1995 and undated
    - Articles, 1971-1973 and undated (Box S1)
    - California justice system publications, 1972 and undated (Box S1)
    - California justice system publications, 1972-1973 (Box S1)
    - California probation statistics, 1971 (Box S1)
    - California Youth Authority monthly statistics, 1972 Aug. (Box S1)
    - California Youth Authority publications, 1969-1972 and undated, 3 folders (Box S1)
    - Clippings, 1972 and undated (Box S1)
    - Correspondence and papers, 1972 and undated (Box S1)
    - Edward Jackson, Petition for Writ of Habeus Corpus, circa 1972 (Box S1)
    - French prisons clipping, undated (Box S1)
    - From Soledad to San Quentin pamphlet, circa 1973 (Box S1)
    - Inmates of Sybil Brand Institute for Women v. Pitchess, lawsuit, 1973, 2 folders (Box S1)
    - Model Act for the Protection of Rights of Prisoners, 1972 (Box S1)
    - Notes and correspondence, 1973 and undated (Box S1)
    - Prisoners' Union, 1973 and undated (Box S2)
    - Prison Law Project, publicity on George Jackson, 1970-1973 and undated, 2 folders (Box S2)
    - Prisons and Ghettoes, reprinted sermon, 1991 (Box S2)
    - The Psychological Power and Pathology of Imprisonment article 1971 (Box S2)
    - Ramparts article on George Jackson, 1973 Apr. (Box S2)
    - Sheila Ryan and New Bedford Correctional Facility, 1994 and undated (Box S2)
    - Sheila Ryan DeLuca, 1994 (Box S2)
    - Women, 1973 and undated (Box S2)
    - Women in Prison article, 1971 June (Box S2)
    - Women in Prison conference, 1974 (Box S2)
    - Women's Prison Association, A Study in Neglect, 1972 (Box S2)
    - Women prisoners, 1974-1984 and undated (Box S2)
    - Women Prisoners Convicted by Drugging, correspondence and Daisy Benson papers, 1992-1995 (Box S2)
  - Psychiatric Survivors Movement, 1962-1998 and undated
    - Activists for Alternatives - Seth Farber, 1989-1990 (Box S2)
    - Against Shock, 1990 and undated (Box S2)
    - American Psychiatric Association meeting, debate and Support-In, 1990 (Box S2)
    - American Psychiatric Association debate on medical model, 1990
      - APA debate, file names Apadebat and Apadebat.bk!, 1991 Mar. 15 (Disk018) (Box S2)
    - American Psychological Association annual meeting, 1990 (Box S2)
    - Anti-psychiatry articles, 1966-1990 and undated, 3 folders (Box S2)
    - Brainwashing articles, 1962-1994 and undated (Box S2)
    - Charlotte Perkins Gilman Project, 1991 (Box S2)
    - Coalition against Coercive Psychiatry, undated (Box S2)
    - Conferences, 1991 and undated (Box S2)
    - Correspondence and documents from an ex-mental patient, 1990 (Box S3)
    - "Crazy," 1997 (Box S3)
    - "Crazy Medicine," 1990 (Box S3)
    - Crazy Women video, undated (Box S3)
    - Fleming v. Reid legal opinion on involuntary treatment, 1991 (Box S3)
    - Foucault tribunal, German poster, 1998 (Box S3)
    - The Helpful Friend or Relative manuscript, 1989 (Box S3)
    - Israeli Association against Psychiatric Assault, 1997-1998 and undated (Box S3)
    - "Little Library of Dangerous Thoughts" bibliography, 1989-1991 and undated
      - Letter to Sue Powell Bernstein on the Little Library, file name Litlibdt, 1991 May 25 (Disk019) (Box S3)
    - "Mad," 1997-1998 (Box S3)
    - "Mad Lady's Poem - China Report," undated (Box S3)
    - "Mad movement," 1988 and undated (Box S3)
    - Madness network, articles and information, 1985-1988 (Box S3)
    - Materials for the Voice piece, 1987-1990 and undated (Box S3)
    - "Mental Health," 1989-1990 (Box S3)
    - Mental Health Bill - Vermont, 1989-1990 (Box S3)
    - Mid-Hudson Peer Advocates/ PEOPLE and Portland Coalition for the Psychiatrically Labeled, 1990 (Box S3)
    - "My Own Madness Network," 1988-1989 and undated (Box S3)
    - Names and addresses, undated (Box S3)
    - National Alliance of Mental Patients/ National Association of Psychiatric Survivors, 1987-1992 and undated, 2 folders (Box S3)
    - National Association of Psychiatric Survivors (NAPS), 1991-1993 and undated (Box S4)
    - NAPS, 1993-1994 (Box S4)
    - NAPS position paper - medical model, 1990 (Box S4)
    - National Association for Rights Protection and Advocacy (NARPA) conference, 1990 (Box S4)
    - NARPA book sales, circa 1990 (Box S4)
    - National Mental Health Consumers' Association conference, 1989 (Box S4)
    - Network against Psychiatric Assault (NAPA), 1974-1975 and undated (Box S4)
    - "New York madness," 1991, 1998 and undated (Box S4)
    - Newsletters, 1989-1990 and undated, 2 folders (Box S4)
    - Notes - Elaine Showalter, The Female Malady, undated (Box S4)
    - Notes on restraint, 1989 (Box S4)
    - Peter Breggin versus the National Alliance for the Mentally Ill, 1987 (Box S4)
    - Philip Kumin portfolio, 1989 (Box S4)
    - "Proposal/Concept for a tribunal on state of human rights in psychiatry," undated (Box S4)
    - Psychiatric Survivors Movement
      - 1986-1988 and undated, 2 folders (Box S4)
      - 1989 and undated (Box S4)
      - 1990 and undated, 2 folders (Box S4)
      - 1991-1992 (Box S4)
    - Psychiatric Survivors Movement (Box S5)
      - 1992-1993 and undated (Box S5)
      - 1993-1995 (Box S5)
      - 1997-1998 (Box S5)
    - Recovery and Re-emergence journal, 1987 (Box S5)
    - Shock Treatment, 1990-1991 (Box S5)
    - Shulamith Firestone, 1989 and undated
      - Letter to Shulamith Firestone, file name Shulie, 1990 Jan. 16 (Disk017) (Box S5)
      - Letter to Shulamith Firestone, file name Shulie-2, 1990 Feb. 15 (Disk017) (Box S5)
    - Women's Mental Health conference, 1991-1992 (Box S5)
  - Torture, 1974-1999 and undated
    - Amnesty International, 1985 and undated (Box S5)
    - Apple Valley Books, books on South America, 1991 (Box S5)
    - Articles, 1980, 1990-1992 and undated (Box S5)
    - Articles, 1985-1992 and undated (Box S5)
    - Articles on the Philippines, 1976-1984 and undated (Box S5)
    - Bosnia rape and torture, 1992-1993 and undated (Box S5)
    - California trip/ torture in the Philippines, 1986-1987 and undated (Box S5)
    - The Center for Victims of Torture, 1987-1991 and undated (Box S5)
    - Clippings, 1986 (Box S5)
    - Clippings, 1990-1992 (Box S5)
    - Clippings and notes, 1986-1988 and undated (Box S5)
    - Clippings and "Rehabilitating Victims of Torture" typescript, 1983 and undated (Box S5)
    - Clippings - theories of power and government, 1986 and undated (Box S5)
    - French trip/ 100 pieces and Bataille, 1990 (Box S5)
    - Hitler and Nazis, 1986-1992 and undated (Box S5)
    - Human rights information, 1977 and undated, 2 folders (Box S5)
    - Mexico travel, 1987, 2 folders (Box S5)
    - Nicaragua Contras, 1986-1987 and undated (Box S5)
    - Notes, circa 1980s (Box S5)
    - Notes (Box S6)
      - 1990 and undated (Box S6)
      - Circa 1990s (Box S6)
      - ASEL, undated (Box S6)
      - Alexsandr Solzhenitsyn, undated (Box S6)
      - Amnesty, Torture in the '80s, undated (Box S6)
      - Edward Peters, History of Torture, undated (Box S6)
      - Elaine Scarey, The Body in Pain, undated (Box S6)
      - Ideas around Peters theory, talk with friends, undated (Box S6)
      - Lanzman's Showah, undated (Box S6)
      - Political Economy of Torture, undated (Box S6)
      - Primo Levi and Horst Krieger, 1986 and undated (Box S6)
      - "Seminal," undated (Box S6)
    - Palestine, 1986 (Box S6)
    - Peru, 1992 (Box S6)
    - Political prisoners
      - 1975-1985 and undated, 2 folders (Box S6)
      - Chile and Latin America, 1974-1977, 1992 and undated (Box S6)
      - Iran, 1974 and undated (Box S6)
      - Italy and Germany, 1979-1980 and undated (Box S6)
      - Russia, 1980 (Box S6)
      - U.S., 1979-1982 and undated (Box S6)
      - U.S., 1987-1991 and undated (Box S6)
      - Women in Spain, 1974-1975 (Box S6)
    - Pornography (from Catherine MacKinnon), 1984-1985 (Box S6)
    - Reza Baraheni, Statement on human rights in Iran, 1976 Sept. 8 (Box S6)
    - Scraps, undated (Box S6)
    - South Africa, 1985-1990 and undated (Box S6)
    - "The State," 1986 and undated (Box S6)
    - Terrorism notes, undated (Box S6)
    - Torture, 1982-1984 and undated (Box S6)
    - Torture, 1984-1985 and undated (Box S7)
    - Torture, 1987-1991 and undated, 2 folders (Box S7)
    - U.N. Human Rights for Women, 1993-1994 and undated (Box S7)
    - U.N. Human Rights for Women/ Charlotte Bunch, 1992-1994 (Box S7)
    - Unicef on children, 1992 (Box S7)
    - University of Chicago conference, 1999 Mar., 2 folders (Box S7)
    - University of Chicago conference papers, 1999 (Box S7)
  - Travel, 1974-1998 and undated
    - Brussels - Luxembourg, 1980 and undated (Box S7)
    - Eastern Airlines dispute, 1979-1980 (Box S7)
    - Europe and Ireland travel planning, undated (Box S7)
    - German book tour, 1993 (Box S7)
    - Hotel advertisements, 1981 and undated (Box S7)
    - Italy and Paris travel, 1974 and undated (Box S7)
    - Italy - correspondence, notes, clippings, 1975-1977, 1991 and undated, 2 folders (Box S7)
    - Italy - il Palio brochure, 1974 (Box S7)
    - Italy - postcards, circa 1974 (Box S7)
    - Italy visit, 1996 (Box S7)
    - London and Paris correspondence, 1975 (Box S7)
    - Minneapolis/St. Paul brochures, 1978-1986 and undated (Box S8)
    - Minneapolis/St. Paul map and notes, 1974 (Box S8)
    - Netherlands brochures, 1977-1980 and undated (Box S8)
    - Notes, receipts, and old passports, 1975-1980 and undated (Box S8)
    - Paris, 1985-1986 and undated (Box S8)
    - Paris trip, 1980 (Box S8)
    - Paris trip, 1981 (Box S8)
    - Paris trip, 1982 (Box S8)
    - Paris trip, 1998 (Box S8)
    - "Pie in the Sky" [Airline frequent flyer programs], 1992-1994 (Box S8)
    - Spain trip, 1983 and undated (Box S8)
    - Travel clippings, 1981-1986 (Box S8)
    - Travel club, 1974-1977 (Box S8)
    - "Year of the French," 1983-1984 and undated (Box S8)
  - Women's Archives Project, 1990-1993 and undated
    - Charity Begins at Home photocopy, 1990 (Box S8)
    - Electronic format only: "Women's Archives Project: Charter of a Film Company Dedicated to Documenting the Women's Movement," 1991
      - file name Videochr, 1991 Mar. 28 (Disk017) (Box S8)
    - Draft incorporation papers, 1992 (Box S8)
    - Examples of women's workshops, 1990-1992 and undated (Box S8)
    - Fundraising, 1991-1992 and undated, 2 folders (Box S8)
    - Fundraising contacts, 1992 and undated (Box S8)
    - Getty Center material, 1992 (Box S8)
    - Grants, 1991 and undated (Box S8)
    - Jennifer's foundation list, 1992 (Box S8)
    - New York Foundation for the Arts, 1992 (Box S8)
    - New York Foundation for the Arts, 1993 (Box S8)
    - Note - "The Great Historical Project," undated (Box S8)
    - Our packet, 1991 and undated (Box S8)
    - Pollock-Krasner Foundation, 1992 (Box S8)
    - Proposal and notes, circa 1991 (Box S8)
    - Ti-Grace's grant, 1992 and undated (Box S8)
    - Very professional grant proposal example - National Association of Psychiatric Survivors, 1992 (Box S8)
    - Video, 1990-1992 and undated (Box S9)
    - Video catalog, 1991 (Box S9)
  - Women's Rights Movement, 1965-1981 and undated
    - Abortion rights pamphlet and resource list, 1969 and undated (Box S9)
    - Barnard Bulletin debates, 1967 (Box S9)
    - Barnard campus strike, 1968 (Box S9)
    - The Burning Bra paper, 1970 (Box S9)
    - Columbia University faculty report on women, circa 1970 (Box S9)
    - Columbia University Women's Liberation, 1969 and undated (Box S9)
    - Columbia University Women's Liberation Curriculum Committee, 1970 and undated (Box S9)
    - Cornell University campus activism, 1969 (Box S9)
    - Cornell University Conference on Women, 1968-1969 and undated (Box S9)
    - Cornell University conference on women, clippings, 1969 (Box S9)
    - England, 1975-1981 (Box S9)
    - Japan, 1971-1974 (Box S9)
    - Joan Hoff Wilson, Women's Studies and Feminism: Survival in the Seventies, 1973 May 26 (Box S9)
    - Membership lists, New York, circa 1968 (Box S9)
    - The Militant and New York Free Press clippings, 1969-1970 (Box S9)
    - Newsletters, 1968-1974 (Box S9)
    - Notes - women as prisoners of medical profession, 1973 (Box S9)
    - National Organization for Women (NOW), 1967 and undated (Box S9)
    - NOW, 1967-1968 and undated (Box S9)
    - NOW, 1968 and undated (Box S9)
    - NOW, 1974,1976 and undated (Box S9)
    - NOW - Abortion, 1967-1968 and undated (Box S9)
    - NOW Education Committee, 1968-1969 and undated, 3 folders (Box S10)
    - NOW Employment Committee - Sex Segregation in Job Advertising, 1968 and undated (Box S10)
    - National Women's Political Caucus, 1971-1972 and undated (Box S10)
    - New York Radical Women Group 2 - listing, undated (Box S10)
    - Professional Women's Caucus (PWC), 1971 (Box S10)
    - Reports on Women in Higher Education, 1970, 1 of 2 folders (Box S10)
    - Reports on Women in Higher Education, 1970, 2 of 2 folders (Box S10)
    - Sacramento State University, Women's Studies Board, 1973 and undated (Box S10)
    - Seattle International Women's Day Celebration, 1973 (Box S10)
    - Sexual Politics article in Notes from the Second Year, 1970 (Box S10)
    - Sheila Tobias, undated (Box S10)
    - State University of New York - Buffalo, 1968-1969 and undated (Box S10)
    - Women, 1973-1974 and undated (Box S10)
    - Women's History Research Center, 1971-1972 and undated (Box S10)
    - Women's History Research Center, 1973 and undated (Box S10)
    - Women's National Abortion Conference, 1971 July (Box S10)
    - Women's rights movement, 1965-1969 and undated (Box S10)
    - Women's rights movement, 1968-1969 and undated, 4 folders (Box S10)
    - Women's rights movement, 1970 and undated, 2 folders (Box S11)
    - Women's rights movement, 1974-1975 and undated (Box S11)
    - Women's rights movement, 1976 and undated (Box S11)
    - Women's salaries – calculations, circa 1967 (Box S11)
  - General Subject Files, 1956-2002 and undated; 1970-1999
    - Abortion, 1979-1992 and undated (Box S11)
      - Book review by Carol Burbank, file names Abortion and Abortion.bk!, 1990 July 11 (Disk018) (Box S11)
    - Abortion, 1998 (Box S11)
    - Adam and Eve catalog, 1978 (Box S11)
    - Advertising - feminist media, 1981 and undated (Box S11)
    - AIDS, 1987 and undated (Box S11)
    - "AIDS: A Project," 1993 and undated (Box S11)
    - American Federation of Television and Radio Artists correspondence, 1979 (Box S11)
    - American Friends of St. Hilda's College, 1987-1992 and undated (Box S11)
    - Angela Davis writings, 1970-1972 and undated (Box S11)
    - Announcements - feminism and women's writing, 1975-1999 and undated (Box S11)
    - Anti-Moral Majority, undated (Box S11)
    - Anti-nuclear activism, 1979-1985 and undated (Box S11)
    - Anti-war activism, 1982 (Box S11)
    - Art, 1982-1985 and undated (Box S11)
    - Articles, Diane Alstad, 1978-1982 (Box S11)
    - Artists Network for Mumia Abu-Jamal, 1998-1999 (Box S11)
    - Art shows, circa 1968 and 1969 (Box S11)
    - Art shows, 1969 and 1974 (Box S11)
    - Art shows and avant garde, 1977, 1992-1993 and undated (Box S11)
    - Art shows and events, 1974 (Box S11)
    - Art shows and events, 1987 (Box S11)
    - Art shows and events, 1990-1991 (Box S11)
    - ASPASIE petition on prostitution, 1991 Mar. 28 (Box S11)
    - Atlanta child murder clippings, 1981 and undated (Box S11)
    - Baby M - Surrogate motherhood, Mary Beth Whitehead case, 1987 (Box S11)
    - Battered wives, 1975-1983 and undated (Box S11)
    - Beijing Women's Conference report, 1996 (Box S11)
    - Betty Friedan, How to Get the Women's Movement Moving Again, 1985 Nov. 3 (Box S11)
    - Electronic format only: Bibliography, 1991
      - file name Refer, 1991 July 19 (Disk017) (Box S11)
    - Bisexuality organizations, 1974-1978 and undated (Box S11)
    - Black Panthers solicitation letter, 1976 July 5 (Box S12)
    - Book and poster sales - women's bookstores, Europe, 1980-1982 and undated (Box S12)
    - Book catalogs, 1977-1978 and undated (Box S12)
    - Book catalogs, 1973-1998, 2 folders (Box S12)
    - Book catalogs, 1986-1990 (Box S12)
    - Books to order, 1990 and undated (Box S12)
    - Bruce Isaacson, press kit, circa 1989 (Box S12)
    - California Master Plan for Higher Education, 1973 (Box S12)
    - "Cazenovia," 1976 (Box S12)
    - Center for Adult Life and Learning catalog, 1992 (Box S12)
    - Center for Cuban Studies mailing, circa 1979 (Box S12)
    - Center for Lesbian and Gay Studies, 1991-1993 (Box S12)
    - Centre Audiovisual Simone de Beauvoir, 1983 and undated (Box S12)
    - Child abuse, 1979-1989 and undated (Box S12)
    - Chinese copyright issues, 1999 (Box S12)
    - Christmas party, 1984 (Box S12)
    - Clitoridectomy/Genital Mutilation, 1980 and 1990 (Box S12)
    - Clara Fraser, Freedom Socialist Party, 1980 and 1987-1988 (Box S12)
    - Clipping - Gay community in Toronto, 1986 Mar. (Box S12)
    - Clippings, 1976, 1986, 1992 and undated (Box S12)
    - Clippings - Gender-based affirmative action at Ontario College of Art, 1990 (Box S12)
    - "Collage," 1977 and undated (Box S12)
    - Committee against Repression in Italy (CARI) newsletter, circa 1981 (Box S12)
    - Committee for Artistic and Intellectual Freedom in Iran (CAIFI), 1977, 1985 and undated (Box S12)
    - Computer information, 1991-1992 and undated (Box S12)
    - Crystal Chambers v. Omaha Girls Club legal complaint, circa 1980s (Box S12)
    - Derham Hall, 1975-1997 and undated, 2 folders (Box S12)
    - Dinner at Kate's film proposal ("Chicken Movie"), 1990 and undated (Box S12)
    - Direct book and poster sales, advertising, 1979-1985 and undated (Box S12)
    - Drawing - caricature of Millett, 1990 (Box S12)
    - "Duck Lake Phantasy" [building plans for Ward, Co.], undated (Box S12)
    - Ellen Herman, Still Married after All These Years? photocopy, 1990 (Box S12)
    - El Salvador, 1981-1989 and undated (Box S12)
    - Equal Rights Amendment, 1976-1982 and undated (Box S12)
    - "Eros" [Blush Entertainment catalog], 1990 (Box S12)
    - "Excerpts" [carbons and carbon copies], undated (Box S12)
    - Fellowship of Reconciliation, mailing on Vietnam, 1976 (Box S12)
    - Feminist Anti-censorship Task Force (FACT), 1985 (Box S13)
    - Feminist Center for Human Growth and Development pamphlet, 1979 (Box S13)
    - Feminist grants and funds, 1981 and 1986 (Box S13)
    - Feminist quarrels and follies, 1975-1986 and undated (Box S13)
    - Film proposal - "Critical Mass," 1992 (Box S13)
    - Forum 98, 1997-1999, 5 folders (Box S13)
    - Fund for Open Information and Accountability (FOIA), 1983 (Box S13)
    - Gay Academic Union, 1974-1978, 1990 and undated (Box S13)
    - Gay activism, 1973-1974 and undated (Box S13)
    - Gay activism, 1974-1978 and undated (Box S13)
    - Gay activism, 1978-1992 and undated (Box S13)
    - Gay liberation - Columbia and Rutgers, 1970-1971 (Box S13)
    - Gay liberation - testimony for Bill 475, New York City, 1971 (Box S13)
    - Gay rights - Veronica Berrill clippings, 1995-1997 (Box S13)
    - George Dureau, 1981 and undated (Box S13)
    - Gloria Steinem and the CIA, clippings and press release, 1959-1979 (Box S13)
    - Gray Panthers, 1977 and undated (Box S13)
    - Gulf War protests, 1991 (Box S13)
    - Electronic format only: Halva International, 1988 and 1991
      - Corporate structure of Halva International, file name Chart.wkb, 1988 May 13 (Disk018) (Box S13)
      - Pickford v. Halva, Kentucky legal brief, file names Brief.wkb and Brief.bk!, 1991 Feb. 21 (Disk018) (Box S13)
    - Hamburger Institut fr Sozialforschung, 1985-1987, 1-2 of 4 folders (Box S13)
    - Hamburger Institut fr Sozialforschung, 1985-1987, 3-4 of 4 folders (Box S14)
    - Hannelore Mabry articles, 1984 (Box S14)
    - Heather's drawings, undated (Box S14)
    - Homeless activism, 1985-1987 (Box S14)
    - Homosexuality and prostitution report, British Home Office, 1957 (Box S14)
    - Homosexuality - notes, clippings, and publications, 1971-1974 and undated (Box S14)
    - Homosexuality - Lincoln Gay Action Group, Nebraska, 1971 (Box S14)
    - Honors and awards, 1984 and 1993-1994 (Box S14)
    - Howard Deutsch, 2000 (Box S14)
    - "How to Get Published," 1987-1990 and undated (Box S14)
    - Impact of the Reagan Budget on Women report, 1984 (Box S14)
    - Impeachment - Stop the Inquisition, 1998-1999, 2 folders (Box S14)
    - Inez Garcia case, 1975-1976 (Box S14)
    - Institutes for research on women, 1991 (Box S14)
    - Instituto della Enciclopedia Italiana request, 1984 (Box S14)
    - "Interesting" [clippings], 1974-1975 and undated (Box S14)
    - International Tribunal on Crimes against Women, 1975-1977 and undated (Box S14)